# **BAHADIR SAYGILI**



#### Address:

16/5 Murat Apt. Kart St. Selçuklu Neighborhood 06940 Sincan/ANKARA

#### Tel:

+090 (507) 744 0839

#### Email:

bhdrsaygili@gmail.com

#### Website:

www.bahadirsaygili.com

### Socials:



https://www.linkedin.com/in/bahadir-saygili/



https://github.com/bsaygili

## Summary

Having gained the notion of engineering, I shaped my career by using the industrial engineering education effectively in my professional life.

My interest in software has always been a dimension that excited me inside. I became a self-taught front-end developer. I will continue to learn.

An ambitious, enthusiastic, and learning-hungry front-end developer who cares about all aspects of the user experience using React, javascript, HTML and CSS.

# **Key Skills**

- Project Management
- Leadership
- Effective Decision Maker
- Innovative
- Problem Solver

## **Experience**

- Fanus Media, Freelance Front-End Developer, December 2021 – continue.
  - Developing responsive websites and e-commerce sites of clients with React,
  - Designed website including graphical user interface design and coding,
  - Knowledge of Web standards and protocols like HTML, CSS, HTTP, JavaScript with ES6 and React.js
- Balçık Heting Elements Co., Serial Manufacturing Planning Specialist, September 2018 - March 2022.
  - Making daily production plans,
  - Staff management,
  - Solution to daily problems in production with an engineering approach
- Turkish Air Force, Military Interceptor Officer, August 2014 -July 2018.
  - Preparing Flight Plans
  - Controlling Military Air Traffic
  - Observing Air Field for hostile/foreign Air Traffic
  - Flight with HİK/AWACS for National Interest

## **Education**

- Vocational School of Justice, Anadolu University 2014 2018.
  - Theorotical and practical knowledge with regard to qualificiations required by the justice service.
  - Sufficient knowledge of the law.
- Industrial Engineering, Turkish National Defense University 2010 – 2014.
  - Visual Ergonomics, Aesthetic and minimalist web design, Heuristic Evaluation
  - Sports Complex Layout for the Olympic Games to be Held in Istanbul with the Shortest Path Approach (as a graduation thesis.)

### Front-end Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- Javascript
- React
- Redux

- Bootstrap
- Styled-Components
- Metarial UI
- Git
- NPM
- Webpack

### Language

Turkish: NativeEnglish: Fluent